dropjiffy.com 2017-03-01

# Privacy Policy - Dropjiffy - Secure and Private File Transfer

Privacy of our visitors is very important to us. We do not ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. In our services, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what is visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Dropjiffy.com and how it is used.

Data privacy is an important integral part of our service. Dropjiffy provides its users with an infrastructure, which enables the user to temporarily save electronic files on internet servers. The files saved with Dropjiffy are treated confidentially. Dropjiffy does not provide any search function, with which Dropjiffy's infrastructure can be searched. Dropjiffy does not scan or open the files of its users. Nobody can access your files without knowledge of the complete download link.

All files uploaded by users are stored on one of our servers and are permanently deleted in no more than 31 days since its upload. Please note that access to the download links will be disabled after 30 days of upload.

Like many other Web sites, Dropjiffy.com makes use of log files. We automatically receive certain types of information when you interact with our Web pages, services and communications. This information includes your computer or digital device's IP address, access times, your browser type and language, type of operating system you use, your account activity and accessed pages. These information are logged and used by Dropjiffy.com for measuring usage. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

We use Google Analytics for measuring usage of the site. To learn more about the privacy policy of Google Analytics, [click here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/), and to learn how to opt out of that service [click here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Dropjiffy uses cookies to help Dropjiffy identify and track visitors, their usage of Dropjiffy website, and their website access preferences. Dropjiffy visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Dropjiffy's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Dropjiffy's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

We will not rent, sell or share your information with third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) co-operate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities; (c) identify persons who may be violating the law or legal notice; (d) protect and defend the rights or property of Dropjiffy or third parties; (e) protect the safety of an individual or group; (f) prevent fraud or abuse of Dropjiffy or its users.

The security of your information is important to us. We employ appropriate security measures in place to protect information collected from loss, destruction, disclosure, unauthorized access, misuse and alteration. Although we strive to protect your personal information, Dropjiffy cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of these information by Dropjiffy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at hello@dropjiffy.com

Last update : 07-07-2013
